Preliminary Inventory to the Servas International records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Minutes of conferences, 1967-1995 (Box-folder 61: 1)
  Includes minutes from various conferences: Los Angeles-1976, Demark-1978, India-1980, Israel-1983, Rome-1986, France-1992, and Melbourne 1995.
- Servas annual report, 1976-1990 (Box-folder 62: 1)
- Servas administrative files - EXCO files, 2000-2004 (Box-folder 62: 2)
- Servas correspondence and administrative documents, 1972-1995 (Boxes 63-64)
- Servas administrative files - Office report, 1996 (Box-folder 65: 1)
- Servas - Administrative documents, 1950-1999 (Box-folder 65: 2)
- Servas administrative files - Survival Network, Board, administrative publications, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 66: 1)
- Servas administrative files - Chronology file - Correspondence from the administrators, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 66: 2)
- Conferences, 1966-1996 (Box-folder 67: 1)
- National meetings, 1978-1986 (Box-folder 67: 2-3)
- Host and traveler forms, circa 1990 (Box-folder 68: 1)
- Annual meetings, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 68: 2)
- National meetings, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 68: 3)
- Conferences, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 68: 4)
- Board of Directors, Directors File, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 69: 1)
- Servas history, 1963-1981 (Box-folder 69: 2)
- Articles and clippings, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 69: 3)
- Conferences, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 69: 4)
- Board of Directors, Directors File, circa 2000s (Box-folder 70: 1-2)
- Correspondence, 1951-1960 (Box-folder 70: 3)
- Correspondence, 1961-1970 (Box-folder 70: 4)
- Articles and correspondence, circa 1970 (Box-folder 70: 5)
- Correspondence, 2001-2008 (Box-folder 70: 6)
- Correspondence, Esther Harlan, circa 2008 (Box-folder 70: 7)
- Correspondence, 1991-2000 (Box-folder 71: 1-2)
- Bob Liutweiler, 1980-2008 (Box-folder 71: 3)
- U.S. Servas News, 1973-1990 (Box-folder 71: 4)
- Newsletters, 1978-2000 (Box-folder 72: 1)
- Newsletters, 1993-2006 (Box-folder 72: 2-4)
- Miscellany, 1995-2004 (Box-folder 73: 1)
- Newsletters, 1975-2005 (Box-folder 73: 2)
- Newsletters, 1976-1993 (Box-folder 73: 3)
- Newsletters, 1987-2004 (Box-folder 73: 4)
- Notebooks (writing ideas), undated (Box-folder 73: 5)
- Host list/survey, 1986-1999 (Box-folder 73: 6)
- Printed matter, circa 2000s (Box-folder 73: 7)
- Servas office handbook, circa 2000s (Box-folder 74: 1)
- Staff and Staffing Task Force, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 74: 2)
- Treasurer, 1992 (Box-folder 74: 3)
- Cuny Campaign - United Way, circa 1991 (Box-folder 74: 4)
- Graham, Jo, 1980-1998 (Box-folder 74: 5)
- Servas host files, 1990-1998 (Box-folder 74: 6)
- Servas host files, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 74: 7)
- Servas host list files, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 75: 1)
- Servas host list files, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 75: 2)
- Servas host list files, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 75: 3)
- Floppy disks (Seeds of Servas), undated (Box-folder 75: 4)
- Servas interviewers, 2000-2003 (Box-folder 76: 1)
- Servas "Compas,", circa 2000s (Box-folder 76: 2)
- Correspondence, 1946-2002 (Box-folder 76: 3)
- Negatives, undated (Box-folder 76: 4)
- World neighbors, circa 2000s (Box-folder 76: 5)
- Green House project, circa 1990s (Box-folder 76: 6)
- Environment conservation, circa 2000s (Box-folder 77: 1)
- All People's, circa 2000s (Box-folder 77: 2-3)
- Pro-Active projects, circa 2000s (Box-folder 77: 4)
- Travel reports, circa 2000s (Box-folder 78: 1)
- Servas administrative documents, circa 2000s (Box-folder 78: 2)
- EXCO, circa 2000s (Box-folder 78: 3)
- Writings, 1990-2000 (Box-folder 78: 4)
- Agency, circa 2000s (Box-folder 78: 5)
- Pro-Active projects, 1990-2000 (Box-folder 78: 6)
- English recordings, undated (Box-folder 78: 7)
- Grant, undated (Box-folder 78: 8)
- Peace action, 1987-2004 (Box-folder 78: 9)
- Servas poster, circa 2000s (Box-folder 78: 10)
- Western medicine, 2001 (Box-folder 78: 11)
- Eco books, 1999 (Box-folder 79: 1)
- Servas travel, 1992-2003 (Box-folder 79: 2)
- Health food, circa 1990s (Box-folder 79: 3)
- Liutweiler family, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 79: 4)
- Bob Liutweiler writings, undated (Box-folder 79: 5)
- Pro-Active projects, circa 2000s (Box-folder 79: 6)
- Host welcome packets, 2002 (Box-folder 79: 7)
- International Stamp Record, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 79: 8)
- International Stamp Record, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 79: 9)
- International Stamp Record, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 80: 1)
- International Stamp Record, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 80: 2)
- International Stamp Record, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 80: 3)
- Notebooks, undated (Box-folder 80: 4)
- Notebooks (stories without words), undated (Box-folder 80: 5)
- Report of Indian Affairs, 1994 (Box-folder 80: 6)
- Servas International Newsletter, 1989-2004 (Box-folder 81: 1)
- U.S. Servas articles, 1983-1989 (Box-folder 81: 2)
- Financial Committee meetings, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 81: 3-4)
- Miscellany, 2000-2004 (Box-folder 82: 1)
- Steering Committee minutes, 1978-1990 (Box-folder 82: 2)
- Round Table for Peace and Social Justice, 1986-1994 (Box-folder 82: 3-4)
- Servas in the news, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 83: 1-2)
- Host lists, 2003 (Box-folder 83: 3)
- Host lists, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 83: 4)
- Host lists, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 84: 1)
- Host lists, 2008 (Box-folder 84: 2)
- Old key lists, circa 2000 (Box-folder 84: 3)
- Photographs, circa 1990s (Boxes 85-87)
- U.S. Servas - Memoranda, 1994 (Box-folder 88: 1)
- U.S. Servas - Correspondence, 1994-2009 (Box-folder 88: 2)
- U.S. Servas - Conferences, 1998 (Box-folder 88: 3)
- U.S. Servas - Administrative handouts, 1998-2010 (Box-folder 88: 4)
- U.S. Servas - Meeting minutes, 1994-2010 (Box-folder 88: 5-6)
- U.S. Servas - Financial statements, 2007 (Box-folder 88: 7)
- U.S. Servas - Key people, 1998 (Box-folder 88: 8)
- U.S. Servas - Newsletters, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 88: 9)
- Key persons, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 89: 1)
- Newsletters, 1999 (Box-folder 89: 2)
- Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 89: 3)
- Meeting minutes, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 89: 4)
- Memoranda, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 89: 5)
- Lease documents, 2000 (Box-folder 89: 6)
- Ephemera, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 89: 7)
- Servas - Past guests, circa 1990 (Box-folder 89: 8)
- Servas - Correspondence, circa 1990 (Box-folder 89: 9)
- Servas - Membership, circa 1990 (Box-folder 89: 10)
- Conferences, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 89: 11)
- International, 2006 (Box-folder 90: 1)
- Sherr, 2006 (Box-folder 90: 2)
- Conferences, 1984 (Box-folder 90: 3)
- Host list, 2006 (Box-folder 90: 4)
- Grant Barnes, 2009 (Box-folder 90: 5)
- Interviewers materials, 2007 (Box-folder 90: 6)
- Miscellany, 1998-2006 (Box-folder 90: 7)
- Board meetings, 2007 (Box-folder 90: 8)
- Board, circa 2001 (Box-folder 91: 1)
- Financial statement, 2006 (Box-folder 91: 2)
- Bylaws, 2006 (Box-folder 91: 3)
- Grant Barnes, 2008 (Box-folder 91: 4)
- Mexico, 2000 (Box-folder 91: 5)
- Interview and key person handbook, circa 2000s (Box-folder 91: 6)
- U.S. Servas handbook, 2006 (Box-folder 92: 1)
- Correspondence, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 92: 2)
- Newsletters, 2002-2007 (Box-folder 92: 3)
- U.S. Servas - Financial statements, 2004-2006 (Box-folder 92: 4)
- Servas National Conference, 2006 (Box-folder 92: 5-6)
- Conferences, 2002-2007 (Box-folder 92: 7)
- U.S. Servas database, 2007 (Box-folder 92: 8)
- Printed matter, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 92: 9)
- U.S. Servas and CouchSurfing, 2006 (Box-folder 92: 10)
- Bylaws, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 92: 11)
- Meeting minutes, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 93: 1)
- Servas International Archive Project, 2008 (Box-folder 93: 2)
- Correspondence, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 93: 3)
- Grant Barnes, 2007 (Box-folder 93: 4)
- Servas - General, 1998-2006 (Box-folder 93: 5)
- Office relocation, 2006 (Box-folder 93: 6)
- Administrative files, circa 2000s (Box-folder 94: 1)
- Conferences, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 94: 2)
- Legal/government filings, 1997-2006 (Box-folder 94: 3-4)
- Legal/government filings, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 94: 5)
- Servas - Office files, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 95: 1)
- Servas - Host lists, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 95: 2)
- Servas- Meeting minutes, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 95: 3)
- Servas - Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 95: 4)
- Servas - Newsletters, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 95: 5)
- Servas - Conferences, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 95: 6)
- Servas - Financial records, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 95: 7)
- Servas - Memoranda, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 95: 8)
- Servas - Office reports, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 95: 9)
- Servas - Key persons, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 95: 10)
- Servas - Articles, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 95: 11)
- Servas - Lease documents, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 95: 12)
- Office files, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 95: 13-14)
- U.S. Servas current, circa 1990s (Box-folder 95: 15)
- Servas - Current, circa 2000s (Box-folder 96: 1)
- Office files, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 96: 2)
- Servas, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 96: 3)
- Servas International Newsletter, circa 2005 (Box-folder 97: 1)
- National conference workshops, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 97: 2)
  Note on folder: "What is Servas International? What does it do? Communicate?"
- Servas Mexico, 2006 June 3 (Box-folder 97: 3)
- U.S. Servas and Servas International: Newsletter and correspondence, circa 1990s (Box-folder 97: 4)
- History of Servas, circa 1989 (Box-folder 97: 5)
- Conferences, 2007 (Box-folder 97: 6)
- EXCO newsletters, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 98: 1)
- Conference: Mexico, 2006 (Box-folder 98: 2)
- Conferences, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 98: 3)
- Miscellaneous Servas, 2008 (Box-folder 98: 4)
- The Servas key list, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 98: 5)
- History of Servas, 1999 (Box-folder 99: 1)
- Conferences, 1978-2007 (Box-folder 99: 2)
- Pamphlets, circa 1990s (Box-folder 99: 3)
- Key lists, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 99: 4)
- Newsletters, 1993-2005 (Box-folder 99: 5)
- Host lists, 1992-2010 (Box-folder 99: 6)
- Bylaws, 1997 (Box-folder 99: 7)
- Memos and meetings minutes, 1989-2005 (Box-folder 99: 8)
- Correspondence, 1995-2003 (Box-folder 99: 9)
- Compact cassette tapes and digital media, circa 2000s (Box 100)
- Maine, seminar photos, 2000 (Box-folder 100: 1)
- Servas - Research, circa 1980s (Box-folder 101: 1)
- Servas - Client papers, 1993 (Box-folder 101: 2)
- Servas - Client papers, 1983-1989 (Box-folder 101: 3)
- U.S. Servas - Office files, circa 1980s (Box-folder 101: 4)
- Servas - Client papers, 1991 (Box-folder 102: 1)
- Servas - Client papers, 1992 (Box-folder 102: 2)
- Servas - Working papers, circa 1990s (Box-folder 102: 3)
- Host lists, 1985-1994 (Box-folder 103: 1)
- Servas, 1995 (Box-folder 103: 2)
- Servas - Client papers, 1994 (Box-folder 103: 3)
- Servas - Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 103: 4)
- Servas - Court filings, 1982-1991 (Box-folder 103: 5)
- Servas - Memoranda, 1988-1993 (Box-folder 103: 6)
- Servas International, 1987-1993 (Box-folder 103: 7)
- Servas - Client papers, 1990 (Box-folder 103: 8)
- Host lists, 1984-1999 (Boxes 104-105)
- Office files, 1995-2000 (Box-folder 105: 1)
- Hosts lists, 1998-2006 (Box-folder 106: 1)
- Recruiters, 1999 (Box-folder 106: 2)
- Servas, circa 2000s (Box-folder 106: 3)
- Servas International, 2006 (Box-folder 107: 1)
- Indiana, 2003-2006 (Box-folder 107: 2)
- Motorola standard settings, 2005 (Box-folder 107: 3)
- Wage garnishment, 2005 (Box-folder 107: 4)
- Idaho expert witness law, 2004 (Box-folder 107: 5)
- By-law changes, circa 1990 (Box-folder 108: 1)
- Board retreat: Evansburg, PA, Grant Barnes, legal counsel, 2005 June 3-5 (Box-folder 108: 2)
- EGA, circa 2000s (Box-folder 108: 3)
- Board meeting minutes, circa 2000s (Box-folder 109: 1)
- Office files, circa 2000s (Box-folder 109: 2-3)
- Host lists, 1980-1992 (Box-folder 109: 4-5)
- Ephemera, circa 1990s (Box-folder 110: 1)
- Conferences, 2004 (Box-folder 110: 2)
- U.S. Servas - Offices files, 2002-2004 (Box-folder 110: 3-4)
- Host lists, 1978-1992 (Box-folder 110: 5-6)